[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 6, "question": "Do you still think he's sexy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "think", "he", "'s", "sexy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 7, "answer": "Never you mind.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "you", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "What do you think -- when you sit here in this room, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "--", "when", "you", "sit", "here", "in", "this", "room", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "Well, there's not a day goes by when I don't get up and say thank you to somebody.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "not", "a", "day", "goes", "by", "when", "I", "do", "n't", "get", "up", "and", "say", "thank", "you", "to", "somebody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "How much time do you spend here?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "time", "do", "you", "spend", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "Most of the time.", "answer_tokens": ["Most", "of", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "And do you like it here?", "question_tokens": ["And", "do", "you", "like", "it", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "What do you miss, though, about back home?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "miss", ",", "though", ",", "about", "back", "home", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "I suppose I miss the British cynicism and the humor.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "I", "miss", "the", "British", "cynicism", "and", "the", "humor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Would you plead guilty to that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "plead", "guilty", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "That's a very dangerous question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "very", "dangerous", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "I mean can you remember the names of every woman that you've taken to bed?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "can", "you", "remember", "the", "names", "of", "every", "woman", "that", "you", "'ve", "taken", "to", "bed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "No, no, absolutely impossible.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "absolutely", "impossible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 67, "question": "But you feel guilty that you can't remember?", "question_tokens": ["But", "you", "feel", "guilty", "that", "you", "ca", "n't", "remember", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Quite honest --", "answer_tokens": ["Quite", "honest", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "What's sort the perfect Rod Stewart woman?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "sort", "the", "perfect", "Rod", "Stewart", "woman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I'm married to her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "married", "to", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rod Stewart"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "I did say that, didn't I?", "question_tokens": ["I", "did", "say", "that", ",", "did", "n't", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "So a leggy blond, basically.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "a", "leggy", "blond", ",", "basically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marilyn Monroe", "Brigitte Bardot"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Why blondes?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "blondes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "People ask me that and all I can put it down to is my infatuation with Marilyn Monroe when I was younger and you know maybe Brigitte Bardot, because when I was a kid, you know, preteens and going into teens, they were the two blonde idols.", "answer_tokens": ["People", "ask", "me", "that", "and", "all", "I", "can", "put", "it", "down", "to", "is", "my", "infatuation", "with", "Marilyn", "Monroe", "when", "I", "was", "younger", "and", "you", "know", "maybe", "Brigitte", "Bardot", ",", "because", "when", "I", "was", "a", "kid", ",", "you", "know", ",", "preteens", "and", "going", "into", "teens", ",", "they", "were", "the", "two", "blonde", "idols", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "That potential age gap?", "question_tokens": ["That", "potential", "age", "gap", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Do I look a worried man?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "look", "a", "worried", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "You don't look massively encumbered by stresses of life, I must say.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "look", "massively", "encumbered", "by", "stresses", "of", "life", ",", "I", "must", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alastair"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "How hard when you thought perhaps, you know, it may never work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "hard", "when", "you", "thought", "perhaps", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "may", "never", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "I think we were more or less resigned to the fact that if it doesn't work we've got one wonderful son with Alastair and you know I've been very fortunate -- I mean eight children now so I wouldn't have complained.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "were", "more", "or", "less", "resigned", "to", "the", "fact", "that", "if", "it", "does", "n't", "work", "we", "'ve", "got", "one", "wonderful", "son", "with", "Alastair", "and", "you", "know", "I", "'ve", "been", "very", "fortunate", "--", "I", "mean", "eight", "children", "now", "so", "I", "would", "n't", "have", "complained", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Kremlin", "Penny"], "LOCATION": ["Russia", "Moscow"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "RP", "CC", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Where were you when you heard the good news?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "were", "you", "when", "you", "heard", "the", "good", "news", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "I was at the Kremlin doing a show in Russia, Moscow, and Penny phoned me up and says, we've done it, we've done it, we've done it, and we both just burst into tears.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "at", "the", "Kremlin", "doing", "a", "show", "in", "Russia", ",", "Moscow", ",", "and", "Penny", "phoned", "me", "up", "and", "says", ",", "we", "'ve", "done", "it", ",", "we", "'ve", "done", "it", ",", "we", "'ve", "done", "it", ",", "and", "we", "both", "just", "burst", "into", "tears", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Are you a good dad, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "good", "dad", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "You should ask me kids that maybe.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "should", "ask", "me", "kids", "that", "maybe", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "What have you learned that perhaps you didn't know when you were younger?", "question_tokens": ["What", "have", "you", "learned", "that", "perhaps", "you", "did", "n't", "know", "when", "you", "were", "younger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "The fine line between spoiling a child and depriving has always been difficult for me because I've come from a working class background and now you know wonderful wealth so it's hard for me not to spoil them and it's difficult -- I find it very difficult.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "fine", "line", "between", "spoiling", "a", "child", "and", "depriving", "has", "always", "been", "difficult", "for", "me", "because", "I", "'ve", "come", "from", "a", "working", "class", "background", "and", "now", "you", "know", "wonderful", "wealth", "so", "it", "'s", "hard", "for", "me", "not", "to", "spoil", "them", "and", "it", "'s", "difficult", "--", "I", "find", "it", "very", "difficult", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Do you spoil them, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "spoil", "them", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "How do you deal about price of fame for your kids?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "about", "price", "of", "fame", "for", "your", "kids", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, it's a double-edged sword.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "double-edged", "sword", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "I think that's had a happy ending, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "had", "a", "happy", "ending", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "TEWART: Happy ending.", "answer_tokens": ["TEWART", ":", "Happy", "ending", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Do you feel guilty about it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "guilty", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Yes, I feel guilty about everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "feel", "guilty", "about", "everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "What do you call it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "call", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "We're not weirdoes.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "not", "weirdoes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "No one has ever seen it, have they?", "question_tokens": ["No", "one", "has", "ever", "seen", "it", ",", "have", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Well it's been in magazines.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "it", "'s", "been", "in", "magazines", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Seriously?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "So we can't see it then?", "question_tokens": ["So", "we", "ca", "n't", "see", "it", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "No, no, no, it's really private.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", ",", "it", "'s", "really", "private", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "The size of this room?", "question_tokens": ["The", "size", "of", "this", "room", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "It's the length of this house.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "length", "of", "this", "house", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "How many trains do you have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "trains", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "It's not a question of trains.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "question", "of", "trains", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "People still watching this?", "question_tokens": ["People", "still", "watching", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Singing?", "question_tokens": ["Singing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Did you love that instant chemistry with an audience, the reaction that you got?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "love", "that", "instant", "chemistry", "with", "an", "audience", ",", "the", "reaction", "that", "you", "got", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I didn't get any reaction at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "get", "any", "reaction", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mick"], "LOCATION": ["Eel Pie Island"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What was the moment when you thought, I want to be a rock star?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "moment", "when", "you", "thought", ",", "I", "want", "to", "be", "a", "rock", "star", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Oh, man, probably when I saw Mick and the Stones over at Eel Pie Island.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "man", ",", "probably", "when", "I", "saw", "Mick", "and", "the", "Stones", "over", "at", "Eel", "Pie", "Island", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mick Jagger"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "So you're watching Mick Jagger who the hot rock star.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "you", "'re", "watching", "Mick", "Jagger", "who", "the", "hot", "rock", "star", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "And what did you hope being a rock star would bring you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "did", "you", "hope", "being", "a", "rock", "star", "would", "bring", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "A sports car.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "sports", "car", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "That transformation possess, was there a point when you thought, I've got to do this on my own?", "question_tokens": ["That", "transformation", "possess", ",", "was", "there", "a", "point", "when", "you", "thought", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "to", "do", "this", "on", "my", "own", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Where would all this stuff go?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "would", "all", "this", "stuff", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "Out the window?", "question_tokens": ["Out", "the", "window", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "No, we'd put it in the elevator and sent it down to the lobby.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "'d", "put", "it", "in", "the", "elevator", "and", "sent", "it", "down", "to", "the", "lobby", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 368, "question": "Was there anyone that matched you and Ronnie?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "anyone", "that", "matched", "you", "and", "Ronnie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 369, "answer": "There was The Who.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "was", "The", "Who", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ronnie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "But when that happened, when it just exploded, what was that time like for you because that was stratospherically, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "that", "happened", ",", "when", "it", "just", "exploded", ",", "what", "was", "that", "time", "like", "for", "you", "because", "that", "was", "stratospherically", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "No, that's bullocks.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "bullocks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Would you do it?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "I have gone into the pub for a couple of hours, get a bit of Dutch courage.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "gone", "into", "the", "pub", "for", "a", "couple", "of", "hours", ",", "get", "a", "bit", "of", "Dutch", "courage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "I mean could you imagine doing a duet with her singing?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "could", "you", "imagine", "doing", "a", "duet", "with", "her", "singing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "What do you think of her voice technically?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "her", "voice", "technically", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "I think it's beautiful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "beautiful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "How did you deal with the first negativity that came your way?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "deal", "with", "the", "first", "negativity", "that", "came", "your", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Another dangerous question.", "answer_tokens": ["Another", "dangerous", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Why did they go after you, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "they", "go", "after", "you", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Because I mean look at me.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "mean", "look", "at", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "I supposed the obvious question, do you think you're sexy?", "question_tokens": ["I", "supposed", "the", "obvious", "question", ",", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'re", "sexy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "No, we talked about that earlier.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "we", "talked", "about", "that", "earlier", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "What's the Rod Stewart magic with women?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "Rod", "Stewart", "magic", "with", "women", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rod Stewart"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What to you is sexy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "to", "you", "is", "sexy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "It's an inner thing, it's a look in the eye.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "inner", "thing", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "look", "in", "the", "eye", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Or were you?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "were", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Do you regret that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "regret", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Of course, I do.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 493, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 494, "answer": "So you --", "answer_tokens": ["So", "you", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "I was going to say, I mean, were you just too young?", "question_tokens": ["I", "was", "going", "to", "say", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "were", "you", "just", "too", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "My dad told me.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "dad", "told", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "I mean if you had your time again what age would you get married, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "if", "you", "had", "your", "time", "again", "what", "age", "would", "you", "get", "married", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "TEWART: I don't think you put an age on it.", "answer_tokens": ["TEWART", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "put", "an", "age", "on", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Oh yes, it certainly was, yes, very hurtful.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", ",", "it", "certainly", "was", ",", "yes", ",", "very", "hurtful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Why do you think it didn't work out, when you look back on it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "it", "did", "n't", "work", "out", ",", "when", "you", "look", "back", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "She was too young.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "was", "too", "young", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "Me sister Mary told me brother.", "answer_tokens": ["Me", "sister", "Mary", "told", "me", "brother", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mary", "Rachel"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "NNS", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WDT", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Why did she think that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "she", "think", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I think because my sister Mary understands that women do a lot of growing between 21 and 30, you know, which Rachel probably has.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "because", "my", "sister", "Mary", "understands", "that", "women", "do", "a", "lot", "of", "growing", "between", "21", "and", "30", ",", "you", "know", ",", "which", "Rachel", "probably", "has", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Did it break your heart, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "it", "break", "your", "heart", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Oh, yeah, bloody hell did it.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", ",", "bloody", "hell", "did", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "VBN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Did you feel, wow, this is what it feels like?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", ",", "wow", ",", "this", "is", "what", "it", "feels", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "It was a good six months of, you know, laying upstairs looking at the ceiling in bed, couldn't get out of bed, depression, didn't drink for six month.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "good", "six", "months", "of", ",", "you", "know", ",", "laying", "upstairs", "looking", "at", "the", "ceiling", "in", "bed", ",", "could", "n't", "get", "out", "of", "bed", ",", "depression", ",", "did", "n't", "drink", "for", "six", "month", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "ORGAN: Did you not?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Did", "you", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Didn't drink for six months.", "answer_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "drink", "for", "six", "months", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "How did you get over it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "get", "over", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Well, there's no way of getting over it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "'s", "no", "way", "of", "getting", "over", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "But what were the lessons you had to learn from that not working, that second marriage?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "were", "the", "lessons", "you", "had", "to", "learn", "from", "that", "not", "working", ",", "that", "second", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "Probably, you know, I'm a better listener now than I've ever been before.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "better", "listener", "now", "than", "I", "'ve", "ever", "been", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Penny"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 563, "question": "Do you?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "Yeah, I used to say it, but now I'm all over it like a dirty rag, Penny, every morning, love you darling, I love you pussycat.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "I", "used", "to", "say", "it", ",", "but", "now", "I", "'m", "all", "over", "it", "like", "a", "dirty", "rag", ",", "Penny", ",", "every", "morning", ",", "love", "you", "darling", ",", "I", "love", "you", "pussycat", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Dorchester Hotel"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "But the first moment you saw her, what did you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "first", "moment", "you", "saw", "her", ",", "what", "did", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "Well, it was at the Dorchester Hotel.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "at", "the", "Dorchester", "Hotel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Are you as happy now as you've ever been?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "as", "happy", "now", "as", "you", "'ve", "ever", "been", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Yeah, without a doubt.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "without", "a", "doubt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "But what was it about her that gave you contentment, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "was", "it", "about", "her", "that", "gave", "you", "contentment", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "She's naughty.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "naughty", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Do you think she's the one?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "'s", "the", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "Beyond a doubt.", "answer_tokens": ["Beyond", "a", "doubt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "When you got that call, what were you thinking?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "got", "that", "call", ",", "what", "were", "you", "thinking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Didn't even think it could be cancer.", "answer_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "even", "think", "it", "could", "be", "cancer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "But did you get a sense then of your own mortality for the first time?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "get", "a", "sense", "then", "of", "your", "own", "mortality", "for", "the", "first", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "Yeah, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Did you think to yourself, I could die here?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "to", "yourself", ",", "I", "could", "die", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Yeah, yeah, I didn't -- no, I didn't when I went into the surgery.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "yeah", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "--", "no", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "when", "I", "went", "into", "the", "surgery", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "RB", "VBD", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "What was going through your mind, seriously?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "through", "your", "mind", ",", "seriously", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "I was frightened, really scared, and all sorts of thoughts were going through my mind, you know, of becoming a landscape gardener.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "frightened", ",", "really", "scared", ",", "and", "all", "sorts", "of", "thoughts", "were", "going", "through", "my", "mind", ",", "you", "know", ",", "of", "becoming", "a", "landscape", "gardener", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "Was there a moment when -- like a Eureka moment when you knew you were back?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "there", "a", "moment", "when", "--", "like", "a", "Eureka", "moment", "when", "you", "knew", "you", "were", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "Yes, exactly six months after the operation, five or six month.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "exactly", "six", "months", "after", "the", "operation", ",", "five", "or", "six", "month", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Eureka"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "What was the moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Well, I could do an hour of singing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "could", "do", "an", "hour", "of", "singing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 714, "question": "Outside of football?", "question_tokens": ["Outside", "of", "football", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 715, "answer": "It can include football, but for this audience --", "answer_tokens": ["It", "can", "include", "football", ",", "but", "for", "this", "audience", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "Or are you content now to keep rocking at the level that you are?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "are", "you", "content", "now", "to", "keep", "rocking", "at", "the", "level", "that", "you", "are", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Well, you know, the business has been very kind to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "business", "has", "been", "very", "kind", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "It's extraordinary that you've had this career resurgence on great American songs?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "extraordinary", "that", "you", "'ve", "had", "this", "career", "resurgence", "on", "great", "American", "songs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "Yeah, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 751, "question": "When you had the idea, quite a gamble for you to do that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "had", "the", "idea", ",", "quite", "a", "gamble", "for", "you", "to", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 752, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["'80s"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 753, "question": "Were there people telling you don't do this?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "there", "people", "telling", "you", "do", "n't", "do", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 754, "answer": "First I had the idea in the '80s.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "I", "had", "the", "idea", "in", "the", "'80s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "I'm supposed to do a Christmas album sometime.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "supposed", "to", "do", "a", "Christmas", "album", "sometime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 771, "question": "You can do a country album?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "do", "a", "country", "album", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 772, "answer": "Yeah, man.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 780, "question": "Do you still get the same kick out of touring?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "get", "the", "same", "kick", "out", "of", "touring", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 781, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Rangers"], "PERSON": ["Celtie"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NN", "NNPS", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 782, "question": "Is it still the one thing that is more exciting than anything else?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "still", "the", "one", "thing", "that", "is", "more", "exciting", "than", "anything", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "CD", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 783, "answer": "Well, Celtie beating Rangers is good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Celtie", "beating", "Rangers", "is", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 791, "question": "What is that feeling like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "that", "feeling", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 792, "answer": "I don't suffer nerves like I used to.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "suffer", "nerves", "like", "I", "used", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 799, "question": "How do you know when you've got them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "when", "you", "'ve", "got", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 800, "answer": "You can see it, mate.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "see", "it", ",", "mate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 803, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 804, "answer": "It's tremendous, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "tremendous", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 805, "question": "Is that the greatest feeling?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "greatest", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 806, "answer": "Yeah, yeah, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "yeah", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 807, "question": "ORGAN: Is that better than sex?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Is", "that", "better", "than", "sex", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 808, "answer": "No, no, it's not that good, mate.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "that", "good", ",", "mate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 813, "question": "What would you like your epitaph to be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "like", "your", "epitaph", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 814, "answer": "I'm a celebrity, get me out of here.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "celebrity", ",", "get", "me", "out", "of", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "WP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 816, "question": "Do you have a way you would like to be remembered then?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "way", "you", "would", "like", "to", "be", "remembered", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 817, "answer": "Just as an honest guy who loved his football, just a simple man really who got extremely lucky, extremely lucky.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "as", "an", "honest", "guy", "who", "loved", "his", "football", ",", "just", "a", "simple", "man", "really", "who", "got", "extremely", "lucky", ",", "extremely", "lucky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "If your parents could be sitting now watching this, what do you think they would have thought?", "question_tokens": ["If", "your", "parents", "could", "be", "sitting", "now", "watching", "this", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "they", "would", "have", "thought", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "VBG", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "Well, you know, they saw me break through in the early '70s.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "they", "saw", "me", "break", "through", "in", "the", "early", "'70s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 822, "question": "They would be proud of you as a man, do you think, the way you've evolved?", "question_tokens": ["They", "would", "be", "proud", "of", "you", "as", "a", "man", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "the", "way", "you", "'ve", "evolved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 823, "answer": "Yeah, they would, I'm sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "they", "would", ",", "I", "'m", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 835, "question": "You've lost lots of money?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "lost", "lots", "of", "money", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 836, "answer": "Yeah, not compared to some.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "not", "compared", "to", "some", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 838, "question": "Do you know how much you're worth?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "much", "you", "'re", "worth", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 839, "answer": "Sort of.", "answer_tokens": ["Sort", "of", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 854, "question": "Is there a moment when your pride would say to you, enough?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "moment", "when", "your", "pride", "would", "say", "to", "you", ",", "enough", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 855, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barnett"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 857, "question": "What would be the worst thing for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "be", "the", "worst", "thing", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 858, "answer": "The Barnett (ph) going.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Barnett", "(", "ph", ")", "going", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 859, "question": "Bald?", "question_tokens": ["Bald", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 860, "answer": "I don't know how I would cope with that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "I", "would", "cope", "with", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 862, "question": "Do you know what it is?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 863, "answer": "Go on.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 876, "question": "Would you say you're vain on that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "say", "you", "'re", "vain", "on", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 877, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rod"]}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 888, "question": "Are you gay?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "gay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 889, "answer": "Well, it wasn't going to be that, but maybe it's something you want to tell me, Rod.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "going", "to", "be", "that", ",", "but", "maybe", "it", "'s", "something", "you", "want", "to", "tell", "me", ",", "Rod", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 890, "question": "No, no, it's actually whether you're still wearing women's underwear?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "it", "'s", "actually", "whether", "you", "'re", "still", "wearing", "women", "'s", "underwear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 891, "answer": "No, not today I'm not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "today", "I", "'m", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110330pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 897, "question": "For what period of time were you wearing women's underwear?", "question_tokens": ["For", "what", "period", "of", "time", "were", "you", "wearing", "women", "'s", "underwear", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 898, "answer": "Just for one show.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "for", "one", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]